[Music]
walking down the pool and dark at
night you I'm my mind I don't know that
it's no good for
[Music]
me they say love is just a waste of
time I'll never know now I'm just a
lonely that
[Music]
I want you I want
you I want you I want
you I want you I want you
[Music]
I want you I want
you
dream it all
way I want
[Music]
to I want to
T and unpoke and the all
night and a crowded bar with the Misfits
and the movie
[Music]
stars The Stranger case finds me in the
dark with a broken heart I can help
better I wonder where you are
[Music]
I want you I want
you I want
[Music]
you I want you I want you
I want you I want
[Music]
you love feels like a faded
photograph it's in the past now you just
defeated
memory no you're just a in
[Music]
memory now you're just a fated
memory I want you I want
you I want you I want you
[Music]
I I want you I want
you I do you I want you I want you I
want you
[Music]